<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<PlacesOfInterest>
    <state id="1">
        <name> Abia </name>
        <slogan> God\'s Own State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="abiriba">
                <sitename> Abiriba Village </sitename>
                <description> 
                    Every year, the Abriba community participates in a ritual called "Itu Eye," which is loosely translated as "to announce the law". 
                    It's important to remember that the Abriba 'Itu Eye' ceremonial dates back roughly 600 years.
                    The Abriba community welcomes a new year with the Itu Eye ceremony. The Itu Eye ritual gives the Abriba residents of Abia State a chance to pass new legislation for the Abriba community.                
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    The culture of the Abiriba people is incredibly rich, and the community's culture is heavily influenced by their beliefs. A historic tree in the middle of the village of Abiriba is revered
                     by the locals who live there. The name of the tree, "Okpu Achi," roughly translates to "The achi tree." According to legend, the entire Abiriba in Abia state would be flooded if the Okpu 
                     Achi ever fell. The Ishimokoto river is revered by the Abiriba people as well. The idea is that foreigners attempted to leave the neighborhood using water from the Ishimokoto River. 
                     By breaking the bottle holding the water and watching the water fly back, the natives explained the powers of the river..
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Abiriba is a very interesting place full of life and culture. we believe that abiriba is a place best enjoyed in the sumer or during the numerous festival being held there.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="2">
        <name> Abuja </name>
        <slogan> Centre Of Unity </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite3 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc3</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="3">
        <name> Adamawa </name>
        <slogan> Land Of Beauty </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="sukur">
                <sitename> Sukur Cultural Landscape </sitename>
                <description>
                    The Sukur Cultural Landscape is a remarkably intact physical expression of a society and its spiritual and material culture. 
                    It includes the Palace of the Hidi (Chief) on a hill that dominates the villages below, the terraced fields and their sacred symbols, 
                    and the extensive remains of a former flourishing iron industry.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    The Sukur Cultural Landscape is a remarkably intact physical expression of a society and its spiritual and material culture. 
                    It includes the Palace of the Hidi (Chief) on a hill that dominates the villages below, the terraced fields and their sacred symbols, and the extensive remains of 
                    a former flourishing iron industry.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    The remains of iron-smelting furnaces, which are shaft-type furnaces equipped with bellows, are another crucial aspect of the settlement, which is present in every home
                     of a person who works as a blacksmith. All of the settlement's aforementioned characteristics serve as a historical record of the Sukur people's political and economic system.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="4">
        <name> Akwa Ibom </name>
        <slogan> Land Of Promise </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite5 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc5</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="5">
        <name> Anambra </name>
        <slogan> Light Of The Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="ogbunike">
                <sitename> The Ogbunike Caves </sitename>
                <description>
                    The tropical rain forest belt's Ogbunike Cave is located in a valley behind the Ogba hills, where St. Monica College, Ogbunike, is located. A long walkway with around 317 steps leading down into the valley where the caverns are situated is thought to have been built by the Anambra State government in the middle of the 1990s.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    A sizable colony of bats of varying sizes lives in the caves. Several locations have streams and bodies of water. One of the tunnels has a stream that exits into a river that is moving quickly (River Nkissa). The warm water from the caves and the chilly river water may both be felt where the river and the stream converge.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Depending on the area where your plane lands, getting to the Ogbunike caverns is not difficult. One may enter a park from Lagos and be transported to Anambra State. 
                    The car enters Anambra state in Onitsha and travels toward Awka, the state capital and the opposite extreme of the state, 
                    from there. One can either drive straight to Ogbunike or highlight at Oyi Local Government on the way to Awka to find a cab that will take them there immediately.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="6">
        <name> Bauchi </name>
        <slogan> Pearl Of Tourism </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="marshall">
                <sitename> Marshall Caves </sitename>
                <description>
                    Nigeria's Bauchi State is home to the Marshall Cave. The British historian P.J. Marshall made the discovery of these caves in the early 20th century.
                    There are 59 homes carved out of sandstone escarpments. Each cave is 200 meters long, 10 meters deep, and 30 and 80 meters wide.
                    The caverns have a variety of lines of rock inscriptions and paintings that were probably made by its original occupants.
                    Although it is apparent that humans formerly lived there and used the caverns as a settlement many centuries ago to protect nearby towns from invaders and wild animals, no one is certain who used them.
                    According to rumors, local native people used the caves as a hiding place from slave raiders connected to the Emir of Bauchi and/or arabic slave traders from the sahara
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Marshall caves are one of those places that leave you asking more questions than getting answers whilst also throwing you into the shoes of those who lived there and their early inclinations. it shows just how vastly adaptable humans could get and how we chose to innovate in dire times.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    These caves are a testament to the ingenuity of africans, being able to carve out a home out of a rock is no small feat and being able to live there in such conditions just shows us that we need to celebrate our versatility as nigerians .
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site id="yankari">
                <sitename> Yankari National Park </sitename>
                <description>
                    In Bauchi State, northern Nigeria, there is a sizable wildlife area called Yankari Game Reserve. A large diversity of flora and wildlife may be found there, together with various natural warm water springs, which occupy an area of roughly 2,244 square kilometers (866 sq mi).
                    Because of its prime location in the center of the West African savanna, it offers travelers and vacationers a singular opportunity to observe animals in its natural setting.                                
                    The last of Nigeria's elephants and lions reside there. The Bauchi State Government is in charge of its administration.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    One of the greatest populations of elephants still present in West Africa and Nigeria is found in Yankari. There are between 100 and 150 elephants in this group, which is reportedly the only one that is still alive in Nigeria. Additionally, the Yankari Game Reserve is home to a sizeable population of buffalo, hippopotamuses, roan and hartebeest in addition to the critically endangered West African lion (one of just four known living populations).
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Yankari National Park also features four warm water springs, due to underground geothermal activity. The camp is named after the most well-known of these, the Wikki Spring, with “Wikki” meaning “where are you from the local Duguri language? ”. The Wikki Warm Spring is the largest spring with a width of about 13.0 meters and a depth of 1.9 metres. It flows 21,000,000 liters of clear, spring water into the Gaji River daily. During the day and night, the spring has a constant temperature of 31.1 ° C throughout the year, and was developed for recreation.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="7">
        <name> Bayelsa </name>
        <slogan> Glory Of All Lands </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite8 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc8</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="8">
        <name> Benue </name>
        <slogan> Food Basket Of The Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite9 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc9</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="9">
        <name> Borno </name>
        <slogan> Home Of Peace </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite10 </sitename>
                <description>anydes10</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="10">
        <name> Cross River </name>
        <slogan> The People\'s Paradise </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> Tinapa Resort </sitename>
                <description>anydesc11</description>
            </site>
            <site>
                <sitename> Obudu Cattle Ranch </sitename>
                <description>anydesc11</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="11">
        <name> Delta </name>
        <slogan> The Big Heart </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite12 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc12</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="12">
        <name> Ebonyi </name>
        <slogan> Salt of the Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite13 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc13</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="13">
        <name> Edo </name>
        <slogan> The Heartbeat of The Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite14 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc14</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="14">
        <name> Ekiti </name>
        <slogan> Fountain Of Knowledge </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite15 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc15</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="15">
        <name> Enugu </name>
        <slogan> Coal City State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="ezeagu">
                <sitename> Ezeagu Cave </sitename>
                <description>
                    The Ezeagu Tourist Complex is a half-hour drive from the state capital and is situated in an area of great natural beauty in Enugu State's southern central basin. Exotic plants, a stunning waterfall, a freshwater spring, a lake, and a three kilometer long cave filled with tunnels and chambers are all elements of the complex.
                    The bustling metropolis of Enugu State is a thirty-minute drive from Ezeagu Tourist Complex. One of nature's wonders is on display at the complex. Its area is around 22 hectares, and it includes a lake, a cave, and a waterfall (spring water). Following the purported therapeutic properties of the water from the fall, pilgrims are continually drawn to this location.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Ogbagada's capacity to mark the start of harmattan by making an unusually loud noise from the falls is one of its outstanding phenomena. The over 5-kilometer-long Obinofia cave, whose sheer vastness and compartments are breathtaking, best captures its splendor.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    A few meters away, the thunderous roar of the Ezeagu water rushing down the rock draws attention. The onset of the dry season can be uniquely signaled by the fall through an unusually loud boom. Ogbagada Waterfall and Okpoku Warm and Cold Springs are both well-liked picnic destinations for adventure seekers. The community of Obinofia Ndiuno is a destination for individuals who enjoy adventure.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site id="awhum">
                <sitename> Awhum Cave </sitename>
                <description>
                    There are some locations you go that leave an impression on your thoughts and inspire admiration for the wonder of existence. One of these locations is the magnificent waterfalls, which flow down clear liquid with an audible gushing sound from an unseen source. Nature provides you with exactly that.
                    Enugu state, in the Eastern region of Nigeria, is home to such a natural setting. The name of the waterfalls is Awhum waterfalls.
                    The waterfalls, which are near to the Awhum Monastery and are located in Amaugwe hamlet of Awhum town in Udi Local Government Area, are caused by a large outcrop of granite rock from which water cascades over the top to form a stream.
                    One of the falls' sections.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    The twin cascades of the Owhum Waterfalls are located in a limestone cave that is roughly 300 meters long. From the foot of the cave, a flooded narrow gap swings to the left. 
                    The first waterfall enters the cave around 30 meters from the entrance, and the second and largest waterfall is located at the other end. Small sinkholes in the caves' roofs allowed for elegant illumination, and the running stream down the cave floors sparkled with each beam of light that fell on them.
                    THE AWHUM WATERFALL CAVE IS located in a beautiful scenic community, one that emits a kind of old mystic beauty that leaves one feeling like they have been transported back in time.    
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    It's amazing to see the cave, which was created by a huge outcrop of granite rock. White sand lines the stream's sides as water pours down from the top to create it. The height of the cave is 30 meters (98 ft). All year round, the water that cascades down the waterfall is warm and great for swimming in
                </conclusion>

            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="16">
        <name> Gombe </name>
        <slogan> Jewel In The Savannah </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite17 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc17</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="17">
        <name> Imo </name>
        <slogan> The Eastern Heartland </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite18 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc18</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="18">
        <name> Jigawa </name>
        <slogan> The New World </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite19 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc19</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="19">
        <name> Kaduna </name>
        <slogan> Centre Of Education </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite20 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc20</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="20">
        <name> Kano </name>
        <slogan> Centre Of Commerce </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite21 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc21</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="21">
        <name> Katsina </name>
        <slogan> Home Of Hospitality </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite22 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc22</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="22">
        <name> Kebbi </name>
        <slogan> Land of Equity </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite23 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc23</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="23">
        <name> Kogi </name>
        <slogan> The Confluence State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite24 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc24</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="24">
        <name> Kwara </name>
        <slogan> State Of Harmony </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite25 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc25</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="25">
        <name> Lagos </name>
        <slogan> Centre Of Excellence </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="lekkicc">
                <sitename> Lekki Conservation Centre </sitename>
                <description>
                    THE LEKKI CONSERVATION CENTER IN Lekki, Nigeria, is an oasis of nature within the urban chaos of Lagos, and the suspended canopy walkway that rises over the reserve is the longest in all of Africa.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Six towers that reach more than 22 feet each are part of the canopy walkway. They are linked by a collection of suspended (and swinging) walkways that provide a singular, though rather terrifying, 360-degree perspective of this region of the world from above the treetops. With a length of 1,315 feet (more than three and a half football fields), the treetop walk holds the record for being the longest on the African continent.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Located on the Lekki-Epe Expressway at Km 19. Daily hours for the conservation center are 8:30 a.m. to 5 p.m. For tourists, using the hanging walkway is optional. The walkway requires climbing stairs, so be aware of it. Entries cost N1000.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site id="badagryslave">
                <sitename> Badagry Slave Trade Camp </sitename>
                <description>
                   Through its museums and monuments, some of which date back as far as 1845, Badagry in Lagos State presents a rich history of this region. During the Transatlantic Slave Trade, when tens of thousands of slaves were transported to the Americas and Europe, the town served as a significant outpost. The historical sites in Badagry also reveal a wealth of knowledge about colonial Nigerian society and the introduction of Christianity in the country.      
                    According to Oke-tojinu Setonji, a tour guide and owner of Jinuset Travels &amp; Tours, which organizes excursions to the town's landmarks, visitors come to Badagry to learn about the town that many Nigerians refer to as the "cradle of Western civilisation" in Nigeria.
                </description>
                <funfact>                    
                    There is a well that attenuates the slave's spirit around halfway along the route. There, exhausted slaves might take a drink of water, which, according to Oke-tojinu, traditional chiefs thought would impair slaves' memories and prevent them from remembering their first days on the ships.
                    The slave tunnel, a sizable, spiral-shaped building now under construction by the Lagos state government, is also present near the end of the protracted trip.
                    According to Oke-tojinu, the purpose of the exhibit is to provide visitors with a sense of the difficult journey that slaves were compelled to take.
                    The Atlantic Ocean, with its waves crashing and sparkling in the honeycomb-yellow light, is located next to the slave passage.                             
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    ...
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site>
                <sitename> Tafawa Balewa Square </sitename>
                <description>anydesc26</description>
            </site>
            <site>
                <sitename> Lakowe Resort </sitename>
                <description>anydesc26</description>
            </site>
            <site>
                <sitename> Whispering Palms Resort </sitename>
                <description>anydesc26</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="26">
        <name> Nasarawa </name>
        <slogan> Home Of Solid Minerals </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite27 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc27</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="27">
        <name> Niger </name>
        <slogan> The Power State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="zuma">
                <sitename> Zuma Rock </sitename>
                <description>
                    Zuma Rock is one of the world's tallest and largest monoliths, rising around 300 meters (980 ft) above the surface. The natural monolith is situated in Nigeria's western region, close to Abuja, the nation's capital.
                    Due to the guinea fowls' profusion around the rock, the Zuba people of Niger State gave the rock the name zumwa when they discovered it in the 15th century. The Zuba populace built a community around the rock and grew to regard it as a spiritual guide.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    All we can say about zuma rock is that its hugely breathtaking. nothing else, just breathtaking. shrouded by mystery and spirituality. its semi smooth texture means its very difficult to climb but not impossibe.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    There isnt much to say about  this magnificent rock than how huge it is, its un mistakable and is visible for more than 10 km around madalla and zuba. its largeness is just breathtaking.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="28">
        <name> Ogun </name>
        <slogan> Gateway State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="olumo">
                <sitename> Olumo Rock </sitename>
                <description>
                    One of the main tourist destinations in Nigeria, Olumo rock has a mesmerizing personification. The iconic Olumo rock in Abeokuta stands out among the various tourist destinations in Ogun state. Olumo rock will never stop attracting tourists who are intrigued by how rocks can tell stories on their own because of the rich history that surrounds it.
                    Statues of historical Egba heroes and other emblems of Egba warriors, including Ilesha Abi Agbongbakala, Agaba, the great hunter, Okonkenu, the first Egba paramount monarch, and Jagun Jagun, the sharpshooter and general in charge, are carved into the rock.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Olumo rock is an Edifice that stands in the midst of one of the oldest cities in Nigeria. its magnificence made toglisten with ancient lore and mystery make it that more desired as a place to behold amongst nigerians and international tourists alike.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Olumo rock is a magical enchanted place that tests your imagination and physical ability, leaving you shrouded with curiousity about how the ancient Egba people were able to thrive in such a terrain as well as gifting you a beautiful edifice of a veiw of Abeokuta city from its summit. As Ogun state is the gateway state in Nigeria, Olumo rock cannot be touted as the gateway tourist attraction in nigeria for those new urban adverturers seeking a thrill that isnt situated in a remote part of Nigera. 
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="29">
        <name> Ondo </name>
        <slogan> Sunshine State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="iho">
                <sitename> Iho Eleru Cave </sitename>
                <description>
                    In 1922, while out hunting, a local man named Obele made the discovery of the Isarun cave and immediately returned home to alert the local authorities. It was claimed that this prompted numerous trips to the location, which is roughly four or five miles from the current Isarun.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    The Asarun of Isarun land, Oba Joseph Adebobola Awolehin, commented on the finding of the Cave of Ashes, also known to the locals as Iho Eleru, and noted that it put to rest the claim that East Africa existed before the West African forest was settled. According to him, research done in 1965 by a team of English archaeologists under the direction of Professor Thurstan Shaw demonstrated that the forest fringes of West Africa had been inhabited as early as 9200 BC.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Isarun is a relatively small town in Ondo State, Nigeria. It is located along the Ilesha-Akure road, about 24 kilometers from the state capital Akure, and is only 5 kilometers from its neighboring town Igbara-oke. Although I can't say for sure if this is a legitimate tourist attraction, travellers who enjoy adventure (like myself) should come here. You should be intrigued by the shivers and peculiar mood you experience when exploring a new location.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site id="idanre">
                <sitename> Idanre Hills </sitename>
                <description>
                    The Oke Idanre hill is made up of a high plain with stunning valleys and inselbergs scattered across it. It is located at an altitude of around 3,000 feet. Owa's Palace, Shrines, Old Court, Belfry, Agbooogun foot print, thunder water (Omi Aopara), burial mounds, and grounds make up its physical features.    
                    Additionally, it features flora and fauna eco-systems that are diversified and variable. Very significant biophysical and morphological elements can be found in Oke Idanre, and when these elements interact with one another they produce an enduring cultural environment.
                    Additionally, a group of scientists and field researchers are based on the hill. A colony of bats resides there, and each year the locals celebrate bats with a special event. Many of the movies that are now being made use the hill as a backdrop. The only author to win the Noble Prize for Literature in Africa, Professor Wole Soyinka, also composed his longest poem, "Idanre and other Poems."
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Idanre Hills, with its soaring heights, terrifying gorges, and fatal slopes, is a transitional realm between the sky and the ground thanks to the rich, vigorous ecology at the summit. 
                    Nature is unrestrainedly kind at the top of the hills, with pleasant weather, a clear, sunless azure sky, and a semi-Jurassic rainforest. Tropical rainforest and savannah biomes are
                    mixed together to form the vegetation of the hills. Tall Obeche, green Afara, and Acacia trees stand out among the region's richly varied vegetation, which is also home to a gallimaufry of cactus,
                    cashew, and coconut palms. Under large baobabs, bananas flourish in a lush environment with bamboo. 
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    All in all, the bio diverity, great cultural heritage and folk lore makes Idanre hills one of the most magical and enchanting tourist attractions in the south west and that is why its name echoes tons in the mouths of those who visit the unesco accredited culltural heritage site. 
                </conclusion>
            </site>
            <site>
                <sitename> Akure Forest Reserve </sitename>
                <description>anydesc30</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="30">
        <name> Osun </name>
        <slogan> Land of Virtue </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="ilesha">
                <sitename> Ilesha Kingdom </sitename>
                <description>
                    Owaluse, a descendant of Oduduwa, the ancestor of the Yoruba people, and a grandson of Ajibokun Ajaka Owa Obokun Onida Arara, founded Ilesa in the 12th century. 
                    In Osun State, Ilesa is the biggest town and the seat of the Ijesha (Ijesa) kingdom.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Ilesha much like ile ife is one of the top congrugent towns with very deep cultural history beriddled with mmyth, lore and facts that shaped the yoruba people and 
                    culture into the beautiful and robust way of life that it is today.                
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Ilesha is a gateway town that would lead you to most, if not all of the historical and religious sites of the yoruba people through its lore and culture; you the tourist,
                    would leave Ilesha with more culture and awe than you bargained for.                
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="31">
        <name> Oyo </name>
        <slogan> Pace Setter State </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite32 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc32</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="32">
        <name> Plateau </name>
        <slogan> Home of Peace and Tourism </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="shere">
                <sitename> The Shere Hills </sitename>
                <description>
                    Shere Hills are well-known across Plateau State and the whole northern region of the nation. Military and paramilitary organizations around the nation use the imposing hills for regular training. The state's expansive hills are located in Jos East Local Government Area, a few kilometers from Jos City, the state capital..
                    The various high peaks, with the tallest rising to a height of roughly 1.829 meters or 6.001 feet above sea level, are what draw travelers to the well-known Shere Hills. The Gog and Maggog, two of the hills' highest peaks, are not far from the Mountain School, also known as a center for citizenship and leadership training, where various groups of individuals participate in leadership and military-style experiences.
                    After Chappal Waddi on the Mabilla Plateau, the marvel is a range of undulating hills and rock formations, according to geologist Habila Johnson, who also noted that Shere Hills are a rounded elevation rising over land with local relief of less than 300 meters.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Shere hills are breathtaking and wonderful for those with a thirst for adventure. the beautiful rock formations and teeming veiws make it the best place in Plateau state to get pictures and veiws like none other. its a great place for team bonding events as well as a great stop for rock climbing and hiking enthusiasts.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    Shere hills is just the most diverse place for all sorts of climbing hiking and team building sports letting you to enjoy nature and challenge yourself to see the beauty of what mothernature has given.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="33">
        <name> Rivers </name>
        <slogan> Treasure Base of the Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="buguma">
                <sitename> Buguma City </sitename>
                <description>
                    Buguma is a city and ancient port native to the calabari people of Rvers state. these people were said to have first made contact with colonial masters and had built wealth from selling slaves to both the portugese and british in exchange for weapons and other types of gifts.these items have been preseved within Buguma city and remain a sign of status and wealth.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    The Kalabari peole were warriors who built wealth from fishing and trade with the british and portugese. in buguma cities every street belongs to a certain clan or WARI as they  are referred to locally. the more affluent compounds adorning their streets and gates with ancient canons and sculptures tas a show of wealth and influence.
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    The Owu-Aru-Sun Festival Of The Kalabari KingdomThe Owu-Aru-Sun Alali festival is celebrated by the Kalabari people of Rivers State. It is held in Buguma City in the Asari-Toru LGA and features masquerade and dance displays. Buguma is one of those towns very reminiscent of old times in the collonial era and is a sure way to put you in a nostalgic mood.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="34">
        <name> Sokoto </name>
        <slogan> Seat of the Caliphate </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite35 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc35</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="35">
        <name> Taraba </name>
        <slogan> Nature\'s Gift to the Nation </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site id="mambilla">
                <sitename> The Mambilla Plateau </sitename>
                <description>
                    The Mambilla plateau, located in Taraba State's Sardauna Local Government Area 
                    and rising to a height of more than 5000 feet above sea level, can be compared to
                    an untouched goldmine. The Plateau and its inhabitants have little or nothing to
                    show for this apparent riches in natural resources despite the abundant vegetation,
                    which is reflected in the huge trunks of fruit trees and the cash crops produced.
                    The various rivers that cascade down the Mambilla plateau,
                    the waterfalls, the rich grassland vegetation, the rare flora and fauna of the forest reserve
                    and Gashaka Gumti National Park, and the picturesque mountain slopes and valleys
                    are just a few of the tourism resources available. Other things to consider include
                    the area's residents' vibrant cultural artifacts, customary celebrations, music, and dances. 
                    The development of tourist facilities and resources is necessary. Infrastructure development 
                    on a significant scale is required for the development of tourist facilities. 
                    Increased resource demand and an influx of foreigners will result from this. 
                    To ensure an equitable distribution of the advantages of tourism, it will be necessary to
                    take action to address all of the needs and concerns of the local communities.
                </description>
                <funfact>
                    Besides all the ruckus and inacessibility, if you look at it from that point of veiw,
                    Mambilla plateau is a nautural paradise, of rolling hills gushing waterfalls narrow dirt
                    roads and winding rivers that make it feel like youve landed back in the garden of eden 
                    to chill with Adam and Eve. its that beaurtiful; yet, its remoteness and inaccessibility
                    means it remains untouched mostly, no dirt and littering, low population density, etc, 
                    this makes the place feel like the Nigerian Nirvana. 
                </funfact>
                <conclusion>
                    All in all, Mambilla plateau is a natural haven gem for those who wish to adventure and seek solitude from the bustle of metropoiltan life and is a great place to unwind and feel at home with nature.
                    There are may treasure troves within the area.
                </conclusion>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="36">
        <name> Yobe </name>
        <slogan> Pride of the Sahel </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite37 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc37</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
    <state id="37">
        <name> Zamfara </name>
        <slogan> Farming is Our Pride </slogan>
        <sites>
            <site>
                <sitename> anysite38 </sitename>
                <description>anydesc38</description>
            </site>
        </sites>
    </state>
</PlacesOfInterest>